Come early! Come often!
Schizopolis is a comedy, fantasy, mystery film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
A man works for the unpleasant guru of a Scientology-like movement.
Fletcher Munson, played by Steven Soderbergh.
Right Hand Man, played by Scott Allen.
Mrs. Munson, played by Betsy Brantley.
Corporate Mole, played by Marcus Lyle Brown.
Man in Parking Lot, played by Joe Chrest.
The Mysterious Couple, played by Silas Cooper.
Schizopolis (also known as Steven Soderbergh's Schizopolis) is a 1996 surrealist experimental
comedy film with a non-linear narrative written and directed by Steven Soderbergh.
The film explores themes of assassination, dentist, exterminator.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.